Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 332
    - Local 332 Outgoing Correspondence, January 4, 1949-October 25, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Frank Pincheon to Emspak Regarding Local 332 Officers, January 4, 1949; 6.
      - Pincheon to UE Regarding Dues and Unemployment, 7.
      - John Terry to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 27, 1949-February 23, 1950; 8-9.
    - Local 332 Organization, December 19, 1945-April 15, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak, December 19, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak Secretary to Jandreau, December 26, 1946; 2.
      - Jandreau to Emspak, April 1, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Jandreau, April 15, 1946; 4.
    - Local 332 Fort Edward, February 20, 1956-December 22, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Local 332 Fort Edward General Electric, October 2, 1979-March 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Local 332 Strike, Subsidie and Other Monies, August 22, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Local 332 Legislative Committee and Political Action, April 18, 1961-October 5, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Local 332 Correspondence, May 7, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, May 7, 1946; 1.
  - Local 333
    - Local 333 Officers Lists, December 1946-April 1948 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - List, December 1946; 1.
      - List with April 14, 1947 Josephine Santa Maria Letter to Julius Emspak, April 1947; 2.
      - List, July 24, 1947-April 5, 1948; 3-6.
    - Local 333 Incoming Correspondence, July 26, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - Julius Emspak to Anna Bonarrigo Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 26, 1946; 1.
    - Local 333 Outgoing Correspondence, November 18, 1946-May 6, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - Anna Bonarrigo to James Matles Regarding Finances and Utica Receiver General Electric, November 18, 1946; 1.
      - Biondina Passalecova to UE Regarding Local 333 Officers, September 24, 1946; 2.
      - Josephine Santa Maria to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members, May 6, 1947; 3.
    - Local 333 Ledger, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Local 106 Special Monies and Subsidies, April 13, 1961-August 18, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Local 333 Organization, May 8, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Julius Emspak to Dan Fitzgerald, May 8, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, May 8, 1946; 2.
    - Local 333 Disbanding, June 2, 1948-February 28, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 108)
      - Michael Jimenez to Julius Emspak, June 2, 1948; 1.
      - Jimenez to David Ratner, June 2, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Jimenez, June 9, 1948; 3.
      - Jimenez to Emspak, July 13, 1948-February 24, 1949; 4-5.
      - Emspak to Jimenez, February 28, 1949; 6.
    - Local 333 Correspondence, April 29, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 109)
      - Francis Carmichael to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding New England, April 29, 1946; 1.
  - Local 333 (Schenectady)
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Officers Lists, October 12-December 22, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Incoming Correspondence, July 8, 1954-April 22, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 111)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Rossi Regarding Per Capita, July 8, 1954; 1.
      - Emspak to Anthony Deloreto Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, February 20-March 23, 1956; 2-3.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Al Taft Regarding Local 333 Mica Strikes, 1954; 4.
      - James Matles to Taft Regarding Local 333 Mica Strikes, April 22, 1955; 5.
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Outgoing Correspondence, March 31-April 18, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 112)
      - Albert Taft to UE Regarding Local 333 Mica Insulator Strikes, April 18, 1955; 1.
      - Local 333 President Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 333 Mica Insulator Collective Bargaining, March 31, 1955; 2.
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Financial, January 30, 1952-August 18, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 113)
      - Stamps, January 30, 1952; 1.
      - Charter Supplies, August 18, 1953; 2.
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Chartering, February 2, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 114)
      - Julius Emspak to Lewis King, February 2, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Joseph Infante, February 2, 1952; 2.
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Recharting, August 17-25, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 115)
      - Joseph Infante to Julius Emspak, August 17, 1953; 1.
      - Emspak to Michael Jimenez, August 25, 1953; 2.
    - Local 333 (Schenectady), February 6, 1961-June 6, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Local 333 (Schenectady) Correspondence, October 20, 1953-February 17, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - James Matles to Joseph Infante Regarding Finances, October 20, 1953; 1.
      - Matles to Lewis King Regarding Local 333 Mica Insulator Strikes, November 29, 1954; 2.
      - Matles to Infante Regarding Local 333 Mica Insulator Strikes, April 22, 1955; 3.
      - King to Julius Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, February 17, 1956; 4.
  - Local 334
    - Local 334 Officers Lists, May 7, 1947-April 6, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Local 334 Incoming Correspondence, October 25, 1946-August 23, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 119)
      - Julius Emspak to Bernice Kiper Regarding Dues and Veterans, October 25, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Lawrence Roe Regarding Finances, November 21, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Joseph Sassone Regarding Local 334 Rem-Rand Strikes, July 28, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Elmer Urich Regarding Finances, August 23, 1948; 4.
    - Local 334 Outgoing Correspondence, October 24, 1946-December 3, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 120)
      - Bernice Kuper to General Executive Board Regarding Veterans and Dues, October 24, 1946; 1.
      - Lawrence Roe Regarding Julius Emspak Regarding Local 334 Rem-Rand Strikes and Finances, December 3, 1947; 2.
      - Roe to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 18, 1946; 3.
      - Joseph Sassone to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 31, 1947; 4.
    - Local 334 Ledger, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Local 334 Organization, July 25-August 16, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 122)
      - Julius Emspak to Michael Jimenez, July 25, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, July 25, 1946; 2.
      - Dan Fitzgerald to Emspak, August 16, 1946; 3.
    - Local 334 Per Capita Waiver, April 2-August 9, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
      - Elmer Urich to Julius Emspak, April 2, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, April 8, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Charles Rivers, April 15-30, 1948; 3-4.
      - Rivers to Emspak, May 4, 1948; 5.
      - Michael Jimenez to Emspak, August 3-9, 1948; 6-7.
    - Local 124 Income Tax, May 22-28, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 124)
      - George Callahan to UE, May 22, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Callahan Regarding Income Tax, May 28, 1947; 2.
    - Local 334 Leaflets, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 125)
      - A Strongly Pre-Labor Newspaper takes the UE-CIO Commies to Pieces, 1947; 1.
      - Communism Wins Again in the UE-CIO, 1947; 2.
    - Local 334 Legislative Committee and Political Action, July 12, 1971-October 9, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Local 334, January 9, 1968-June 7, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Local 335
    - Local 335 Officers Lists, December 19, 1947-April 10, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Local 335 Incoming Correspondence, February 9, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 129)
      - Julius Emspak to Albert Roman, February 9, 1949; 1.
    - Local 335 Outgoing Correspondence, November 20, 1946-February 5, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 130)
      - Virginia Becker to UE Regarding Local 335 Officers, Veterans and Finances, November 20, 1946; 1.
      - Floyd Frankson to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 335 Officers and Political Action, May 1948; 2.
      - Frankson to Emspak Regarding Plant Closure and Finances with FInancial Statement, August 19, 1948; 3.
      - Albert Roman to Emspak Regarding Plant Closure, Finances and Local Disbanding, February 5, 1949; 4.
    - Local 335 Notices of Suspension and Delinquency, July-August 1948 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Notice of Delinquency, July 1948; 1.
      - Notice of Suspension, August 1948; 2.
    - Local 335 Financial Report, February 5, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Local 335 Organization, August 19, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Julius Emspak to Lillie Steele, August 19, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, August 19, 1946; 2.
    - Local 335 Plant Closure, August 19, 1948-June 7, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - Julius Emspak to Lillie Steele, August 19, 1948; 1.
      - Steele to Emspak, September 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Charles Rivers, September 22, 1948; 3.
      - Emspak to Michael Jimenez, February 9, 1949; 4.
      - Jimenez to Emspak, March 18, 1949; 5.
      - Edward Landy to Emspak, June 7, 1949; 6.
    - Local 335 Legislative Committee and Political Action, January 11, 1971-November 27, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Local 335, June 30, 1972-November 24, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Local 336
    - Local 336 Strike Subsidie and Loans, December 20, 1978-January 2, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Local 336 Ferranti-Packard, February 18, 1981-May 11, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Local 336 Dunkirk Ferranti-Packard, February 14, 1979- March 19, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Local 336 Strike Assistance, April 7, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Local 501
    - Local 501 Officers Lists, December 19, 1936-January 10, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Local 501 Incoming August Hein Correspondence, October 9, 1936-January 22, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 142)
      - James Carey Regarding Finances, October 9, 1936; 1.
      - Carey Regarding Organization, November 4, 1936; 2.
      - Carey Telegram, May 27, 1936; 3.
      - Carey Regarding Finances and Staff Members, November 1, 1937; 4.
      - Carey Regarding Labor Spies and Depression, January 31, 1938; 5.
      - Carey, March 7, 1938; 6.
      - Carey Regarding Unemployment, March 17, 1938; 7.
      - Carey Telegram Regarding Buffalo Visit, May 31, 1938; 8.
      - Carey Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, July 25, 1938; 9.
      - Carey Regarding Radio Conference, Radio and Chicago, December 12, 1938; 10.
      - Carey Regarding Unemployent and United Mine Workers of America Convention, January 18, 1940; 11.
      - Carey Regarding United Mine Workers of America Convention and Buffalo Visit, February 2, 1940; 12.
      - Carey Telegram Regarding Buffalo Visit, February 15, 1940; 13.
      - Carey Regarding Local 1111 Strikes, March 1, 1940; 14.
      - Carey Regarding Labor History, March 12, 1940; 15.
      - Carey Regarding Novlitt Sparks, March 28, 1940; 16.
      - Carey Regarding Local 416 Kreauter Strikes, May 9, 1940; 17.
      - Carey, June 3, 1940; 18.
      - Carey Regarding United Furniture Workers and Tonawanda Wurlitzer, October 30, 1940; 19.
      - Carey Regarding Factionalism and John L. Lewis, November 13, 1940; 20.
      - Carey Regarding Local 501 Dinner, January 22, 1941; 21.
    - Local 501 Incoming August Hein Correspondence, May 6, 1936-July 12, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 143)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 6, 1936; 1.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, June 17, 1936; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining and Local 103 RCA Strikes, July 7, 1936; 3.
      - Emspak to New Kensington General Electric Strikes, September 14, 1936; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 11, 1936-January 13, 1937; 5-6.
      - Emspak Regarding Labor Spies and Finances, July 9, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding UE Constitutions, October 30, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 511, November 10, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 10-18, 1938; 10-11.
      - Emspak Telegram, August 22, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Membership, December 10, 1938; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Busch Retail Clerks Strikes, December 15, 1938; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 27, 1939; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Aerouox, National Labor Relations Board and Unemployment, August 2, 1939; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, January 10, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and United Office and Professional Workers of America, February 26, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 10, 1940; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding Rem-Rand, Finances and Elmira, June 19, 1940; 20.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Rem-Rand, July 9, 1940; 21.
      - Emspak Telegram Regarding Local 430 Air King Radio Strikes, July 11, 1940; 22.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 430 Air King Radio Strikes, July 12, 1940; 23.
    - Local 501 Incoming August Hein Correspondence, October 16, 1936-May 8, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 144)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 30, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 8, 1941; 2.
      - S. Kelly Regarding Wages, King Colonial and Carlson Stromberg, November 15, 1938; 3.
      - Isadore Lubin Regarding Wages, and Electrical and Radio Industry, October 16, 1936; 4.
      - James Matles Regarding Wages and Gould Battery, May 9, 1938; 5.
      - Matles Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Contracts, July 6, 1938; 6.
      - Matles Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Contracts and Peoples Press, July 6, 1938; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Chicago, Local 102 and Radio Industry, October 20, 1938; 8.
      - Matles, March 23, 1939; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Radio Conference, March 24-30, 1939; 10-11.
      - Matles Regarding New Bedford Aerouox, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and National Labor Relations Board, April 14, 1939; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Rem-Rand Contracts, Local 1237 and Ray-O-Vac, May 2, 1939; 13.
      - Matles Regarding Aerouox, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, National Labor Relations Board and Boycotts, July 12, 1939; 14.
      - Matles Regarding Fedders, July 25, 1939; 15.
      - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Aerouox, July 27, 1939; 16.
      - Matles Regarding Aerovox, Runaway Shops and National Labor Relations Board, August 12, 1939; 17.
      - Matles, September 19, 1939; 18.
      - Matles Regarding Emerson Electric Collective Bargaining, September 27, 1939; 19.
      - Matles Regarding Radio Manufacturers Association, September 27-October 17, 1939; 20-21.
    - Local 501 Incoming August Hein Correspondence, December 17, 1936-January 13, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - James Matles to St. Mary's Contracts, March 13, 1940; 1.
      - Matles Regarding Noblitt Sparks, Wages and Radio Industry, March 26, 1940; 2.
      - Matles Regarding Fada Radio, Plant Closure, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, April 17, 1940; 3.
      - Matles Regarding Fada Radio, Novlitt Sparks and United Auto Workers, April 23, 1940; 4.
      - Matles Regarding Novlitt Sparks, Wages, Women, United Auto Workers and Rem-Rand Strikes, May 3, 1940; 5.
      - Matles Regarding Mailing List, Rem-Rand and National Labor Relations Board, June 21, 1940; 6.
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Air King Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, June 25, 1940; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Syracuse Rem-Rand, September 27, 1940; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Contracts, October 28, 1940; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Farnsworth Radio, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Wages and Farnsworth Fort Wayne Contracts, January 13, 1941; 10.
      - Matles Regarding Marion Farnsworth, Wages, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Women, January 15, 1941; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Plastics Organization and Wages, January 23, 1941; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Farnsworth, Wages and Women, March 13, 1941; 13.
      - Matles Regarding Local 501 Conolial Radio Contracts, June 13, 1941; 14.
      - William Mitchell Regarding Colonial Radio, August 27, 1937; 15.
      - Mitchell Regarding Air King, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, Wages, Pilot Radio and NLRB, March 15, 1938; 16.
      - Mitchell Regarding Wages and Radio Industry, May 11, 1938; 17.
      - Unsigned Letter Regarding Schenectady and Erie General Electric, December 17, 1936; 18.
      - Jim Telegram Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 25, 1940; 19.
    - Local 501 Outgoing August Hein Correspondence, May 21-October 28, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 146)
      - August Hein to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Collective Bargaining, Closed Shop, American Federation of Labor and Aerouautical Union Strikes, May 21, 1936; 1.
      - Hein to James Carey Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Collective Bargaining and Closed Shop, May 22, 1936; 2.
      - Hein Telegram to Carey Regarding Sears Roebuck, May 25, 1936; 3.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, June 2, 1936; 4.
      - Hein Telegram to Carey, June 5, 1936; 5.
      - Hein Telegram Regarding Carey Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Collective Bargaining, June 10, 1936; 6.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Collective Bargaining, June 15, 1936; 7.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Local 501 King Colonial Contracts, Strikes and Erie General Electric, July 6, 1936; 8.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Unemployment, Local 501 King Colonial Contracts and Finances, September 11, 1936; 9.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Supplies with Withdrawal Card, September 29, 1936; 10.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Finances, September 29, 1936; 11.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Membership Drive, October 1, 1936; 12.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Hamilton Westinghouse and Toronto Organization, October 2, 1936; 13.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Radio Industry, October 28, 1936; 14.
    - Local 501 Outgoing August Hein Correspondence, December 1, 1936-January 24, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 147)
      - August Hein to Julius Emspak Regarding Erie General Electric and Company Union, December 1, 1936; 1.
      - Hein to Emspak, December 2, 1936; 2.
      - Hein to James Carey Regarding Local 501 Constitutions and Finances, December 7, 1936; 3.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Erie General Electric, Burke Electric and Erie Resistor, December 8, 1936; 4.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Erie, St. Mary and Hamlton General Electric, December 15, 1936; 5.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 23, 1936; 6.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Stackpole Carbon, Sylvania, Emporium, Erie Westinghouse and Speer Carbon, December 30, 1936; 7.
      - Hein Telegram to Emspak Regarding St. Mary's, December 31, 1936; 8.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 8, 1937; 9.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Staff Finances and Membership Drive, October 1937; 10.
      - Hein to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 12, 1938; 11.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Labor Spies and Trials, January 24, 1938; 12.
    - Local 501 Outgoing August Hein Correspondence, February 1, 1938-July 28, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - August Hein to James Carey Regarding Labor Spies, February 1-28, 1938; 1-3.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Unemployment Demonstration, March 9, 1938; 4.
      - Hein to William Mitchell Regarding Wages, Colonial Radio and Pilot Radio, March 9, 1938; 5.
      - Hein Telegram to Mitchell Regarding Wages and Air King, March 14, 1938; 6.
      - Hein Telegram to Carey Regarding Mass Meeting, March 18, 1938; 7.
      - Hein to Albert Crespi Regarding Finances, May 7, 1938; 8.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Wages, Radio Industry and Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, May 9, 1938; 9.
      - Hein Telegram to James Matles Regarding Philco and Colonial Radio, May 13, 1938; 10.
      - Hein to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 13, 1938; 11.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Wages, Battery and Industry, May 18, 1938; 12.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Contracts, July 2, 1938; 13.
      - Hein Telegram to Carey Regarding Philco Boycotts, August 22, 1938; 14.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Radio Industry, October 7, 1938; 15.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and American Labor Party, December 5, 1938; 16.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Radio Conference, February 1, 1939; 17.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Meisner Coil and Steel Workers Organizing Committee, March 21, 1939; 18.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Radio Conference, Wages, Local 105 and Finances, March 23, 1939; 19.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, March 28, 1939; 20.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, April 27, 1939; 21.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Rem-Rand Collective Bargaining, May 1, 1939; 22.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Fedders, Battery Industry and Radio Conference, May 4, 1939; 23.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Aerovox, July 20, 1939; 24.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Fedders, Aerovox and Steel Workers Organizing Committee Inter-union Rivalry, July 27, 1939; 25.
    - Local 501 Outgoing August Hein Correspondence, August 1, 1939-June 17, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - August Hein to James Matles Regarding Aerovox and National Labor Relations Board, August 1, 1939; 1.
      - Hein Telegram to James Carey, January 24, 1940; 2.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Buffalo Meetings, February 5, 1940; 3.
      - Hein to Telegram to Carey Regarding Buffalo Meeting, February 9, 1940; 4.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Local 1111 Allen Bradley Strikes, February 28, 1940; 5.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Stackpole Carbon and National Labor Relations Board, March 15, 1940; 6.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Noblitt Sparks, Unemployment and Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, March 19, 1940; 7.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Fuda Radio, Unemployment, United Auto Workers and Noblitt Sparks, April 22, 1940; 8.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Strikes, May 6, 1940; 9.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Rem-Rand, May 9, 1940; 10.
      - Hein to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, May 16, 1940; 11.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Rem-Rand and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, May 21, 1940; 12.
      - Hein Telegram to Carey, May 27, 1940; 13.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Tonawanda and Ilion Rem-Rand, June 17, 1940; 14.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 1940; 15.
    - Local 501 Outgoing August Hein Correspondence, July 8, 1940-June 11, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - August Hein to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 501 Officers, July 8, 1940; 1.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Air King Radio Strikes, July 11, 1940; 2.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Tonawanda Rem-Rand Strikes, July 11, 1940; 3.
      - Hein Telegram to Emspak Regarding Air King Strikes, July 11, 1940; 4.
      - Hein to James Carey Regarding Local 1139 Strikes, September 17, 1940; 5.
      - Hein to Emspak Regarding Political Action and President Roosevelt, October 29, 1940; 6.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Wurlitzer, Construction, Congress of Industrial Organization, Political Action and Communist Party, November 1, 1940; 7.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Political Action, John L. Lewis and Factionalism, November 6, 1940; 8.
      - Hein to James Matles Regarding Farnsworth Radio, Wages, Women and Local 501 Colonial Radio Collective Bargaining, January 9, 1941; 9.
      - Hein to Carey Regarding Local 501 Dinner, January 16, 1941; 10.
      - Hein to Matles Regarding Local 501 Colonial Radio Contracts, June 11, 1941; 11.
    - Local 501 Incoming Jerold Mooner Correspondence, July 31, 1943-January 6, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - William Cahn Regarding Taft-Hartley, January 6, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Niagara Frontier Labor Management Council, October 18, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages and General Motors, October 19, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding American Youth for Democracy, April 15, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak, May 11, 1944; 5.